medicalmedium.com 2019-06-14

# Privacy Policy

Anthony William, Inc.  
(Updated Policy Effective: June 4, 2018)

Please take the time to carefully read this entire privacy policy. It relates to the collection, use, disclosure and storage of your private information. By using our website, You consent to all of the terms of this privacy policy. If you do not agree with any term of this privacy policy, please immediately discontinue use of our website. 

## 1\. General Information

Anthony William, Inc. (“we”, “us” and “our”) respects the privacy and security of your personal information. Therefore, we have created this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain how we handle the information we collect when you visit and use any website or online service owned or operated by us, and linked to this Privacy Policy (the “Website”), such as medicalmedium.com. This Privacy Policy covers only information collected on the Website and does not cover information we collect offline. 

## 2\. Collected Information

We may track and collect the following categories of information when you visit and use the Website: (1) IP addresses; (2) domain servers; (3) types of computers accessing the Website; (4) types of web browsers used to access the Website; (5) the referring source which may have sent you to the Website; and (6) other information associated with the interaction of your browser and the Website (collectively “Traffic Data”).

In order for you to access certain areas of the Website, we may require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: (1) Contact Data (such as your name, e-mail address, and phone number); and (2) Demographic Data (such as your zip code). If you communicate with us, for example by e-mail or through a contact page on the Website, any details provided in such communication may be collected as

**Personal Information.**

We also collect other information, some of which may be Personal Information that you voluntarily provide to us when you choose to use some of the Website’s interactive tools and services (“Interactive Tools”). We will let you know prior to collection whether the provision of Personal Information we are collecting is compulsory or if it may be provided on a voluntary basis and the consequences, if any, of not providing the information. By giving us this information, you agree to this information being collected, used and disclosed as described in our [Terms of Use](https://www.medicalmedium.com/medical-medium-terms) and in this Privacy Policy.

If you create an account on the Website, and authenticate the account via a third-party service like Twitter or Facebook, we may collect, store, and periodically update the contact lists associated with that third-party service, so you can connect with existing contacts from that third-party service who also use the Website and services.

We may obtain information about you or your contacts from third-party sources, such as public databases, social media platforms, third-party data providers and our joint marketing partners. We take steps to ensure that such third parties are legally permitted to disclose such information to us. This information may include demographic information (such as age and gender), device information (such as IP addresses), location (such as city and state), and online behavioral data (such as information about use of social media websites, page view information and search results and links). We use this information, alone and in combination with other information (including Personal Information) we collect, to enhance our ability to provide relevant marketing and content to you and to develop and provide you with more relevant products, features, and services.

## 3\. Cookies and Tracking Technologies

**a. What are cookies?**

To make our Website work properly, we sometimes place small data files called cookies on your computer or mobile device. A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another.

**b. What are cookies used for?**

Cookies and other tracking technologies (collectively, “Cookies”), allow a website or service to determine if it was previously visited by your computer or mobile device. Cookies are used to identify users and remember their actions, and for online behavioral advertising. Cookies provide information regarding how a website or service is being used, and help ensure future advertisements will appeal to the user’s interests. 

**c. Our use of cookies**

Generally, we use Cookies to customize content and advertising, improve website functionality and performance, provide social media features, analyze traffic to the Website, and help protect our Website and users. We may use Cookies to collect information about your IP address, domain server, operating system, web browser, and internet service provider. We may also obtain demographic information, such as your gender and age range. Cookies may be used to collect information regarding your browsing history, your use of our Website and the sites of selected sponsors, and your responses to our emails, special promotions and newsletters. We may utilize Cookies to remember your previous data entries and selections (e.g., user name; content delivery preferences), to understand, improve and research products and services, to provide enhanced features, functionality and content, and for the marketing and advertising of our products and services and those of selected third parties.

We use both first and third party cookies. “First-Party Cookies” are Cookies that belong to us. “Third-Party Cookies” are Cookies that another party, through our Website, places on your computer or mobile device. Third-Party Cookies may be placed on your computer or mobile device by someone providing services to us. For example, we may utilize third-party technology services, such as Facebook and Mail Chimp, for data management, marketing, analytics, features and functionality of our Website, and for other purposes. Third-Party Cookies may also be placed on your device by our business affiliates so that they can monitor use of our Website, measure the effectiveness of an advertising campaign, and advertise products and services to you on our Website and elsewhere on the Internet.

Information generated from the use of a Third-Party Cookie on our Website is generally controlled and accessible by the third party. We may also have access to some of the information. First-Party Cookie information is accessible and controlled by us.

**d. How long will cookies stay on my device?**

The length of time a Cookie will stay on your device depends on whether it is a "Persistent" or "Session" Cookie. A Session Cookie is removed from your device once you stop browsing. A Persistent Cookie stays on your device until it expires or is deleted.

**e. How do I delete and/or block cookies?**

For Third-Party Cookies, refer to the third party’s cookie notice. It may offer a means by which you can opt out of the use of the third party’s Cookies. Below is a list of some of the third-party technology services and business affiliates we currently utilize in connection with our Website, and links to policies relating to their use of Cookies and your ability to control Cookies:

>   
>  Amazon  
> 
> Facebook (and its family of apps and services)  
> 
> Google (and its family of apps and services)  
> 
> Hay House  
> 
> Mail Chimp  
> 
> Pinterest  
> 
> Twitter  
> 
> Sound Cloud  

Additionally, your browser or device may allow you to delete Cookies that are already on your device, and block future Cookies (both First-Party Cookies and Third-Party Cookies). However, if you do this, you may not have access to certain parts or features of the Website, and other parts may not work properly. To delete Cookies and/or modify your Cookie settings, follow the instructions provided by your browser or device (usually found within the "Help", "Tools" or "Edit" options).

For additional information concerning control of cookies, and opt out options, visit:

>  Network Advertising Initiative  
>  Digital Advertising Alliance  
>  Guide to Online Behavioural Advertising and Online Privacy

## 4\. Children’s Online Privacy Protection

It is our policy to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), and California Law concerning privacy rights for minors. Therefore, we restrict the Website to persons 18 years of age or older. If you are under the age of 18, you are not permitted to use the Website. If you are a parent or legal guardian of a minor child, you may, in compliance with the [Terms of Use](https://www.medicalmedium.com/medical-medium-terms), use our Website on behalf of such minor child. Any information you provide while using the Website on behalf of your minor child will be treated as Personal Information as otherwise provided herein.

## 5\. Use of Information

We may use your Contact Data to send you information about us and our products, services, policies, terms of use, promotions and events, and to contact you when necessary, such as to schedule a consultation or remind you of an upcoming appointment. We may use your Demographic Data and Traffic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Website, in emails and in other communications, displaying content that we think you may be interested in, and according to your preferences. We may also use information to verify accounts and activity, prevent spam, detect and investigate violations of our terms and policies, maintain the integrity of our products and services, and promote safety and security on and off the Website. 

## 6\. Emails from Us

Sometimes we will send you administrative emails about such things as service changes or new policies. You cannot opt out of these. However, you can always opt out of non-administrative emails. 

## 7\. Disclosure of Your Information

We do not sell any of your Personal Information, nor do we share your Personal Information with any third party for its promotional purposes. We may share Personal Information and Traffic Data with third parties who assist us by performing core services (such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, data storage and security) related to our business operations, or by making certain Interactive Tools available to our Website users. We may also share Traffic Data with our trusted social media, advertising and analytics partners. Third party’s to whom we disclose Personal Information shall be bound to uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality that we have promised to you in this Privacy Policy, and they may only use your Personal Information to carry out their specific business obligations to us. 

We may also transfer information about you to another company in connection with a merger, sale or acquisition by or of our company. If your information will be subject to a different privacy policy as a result of such merger, sale or acquisition, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you prior to the transfer.

The third parties with whom we share Personal Information regarding our Website users are listed below, along with a link to each of their Privacy Policies and a description of the services they provide to us in relation to our Website:

> Mail Chimp  

Services Provided: The collection (via sign-up forms), and storage, of personal data which allow us to create and use distribution lists, send marketing email campaigns, and place online advertisements; the transfer of personal data to certain Mail Chimp sub-processors who perform critical services, such as helping Mail Chimp prevent abuse and provide customer support.

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless we believe in good faith that disclosure of your Personal Information or any other information we collect about you is necessary to: (1) comply with a court order or other legal process; (2) protect the rights, property or safety of our company or another party; (3) enforce our [Terms of Use](https://www.medicalmedium.com/medical-medium-terms); or (4) defend a claim that any posting or other content violates the rights of a third party.

## 8\. Other Sites

This Privacy Policy is not applicable to any third-party website or online service you may be able to access from our Website. Some of these third-party websites and online services may have the look and feel of our Website. Please be aware that you may be on a different website and that this Privacy Policy only covers our Website. These third-party websites may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of these third-party websites. Should you decide to visit a third-party website, we suggest that you read its privacy policy.

## 9\. Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and after we receive it. For example, when you enter sensitive information on our Website, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

Although we make good faith efforts to store Personal Information in a secure operating environment that is not open to the public, you should understand that there is no such thing as complete security, and we do not guarantee that there will be no unintended disclosures of your Personal Information. If we become aware that your Personal Information has been disclosed in a manner not in accordance with this Privacy Policy, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you of the nature and extent of the disclosure (to the extent we know that information) as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted by law.

## 10\. Storage, Correction and Deletion of Information

We store data for as long as it is necessary to provide products and services to you and others. Information associated with your account will be kept until your account is deleted, unless we no longer need the data to provide products and services. You can delete your account at any time. We may store data indefinitely, even after “deletion,” and may archive such information elsewhere. You may access and update your account settings at any time to correct or complete your account information. You may also[ contact us](mailto:info@medicalmedium.com) at any time to access, correct, amend or delete information that we hold about you. We will export your account data at any time upon your request.

## 11\. Privacy Policy Updates

We reserve the right, at any time, to replace or modify this Privacy Policy; so please review it frequently. 

## 12\. Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at info@medicalmedium.com.
